{
    "subject": "resource/Spoetzl_Brewery",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Brewery",
    "human_readable": "Spoetzl Brewery is a type of brewery.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9615616202354431,
            "question": "Is Spoetzl Brewery a type of factory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911415696144104,
            "question": "What kind of business is Spoetzl Brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8722269535064697,
            "question": "Give an example of a product that Spoetzl Brewery makes."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8592785596847534,
            "question": "Can you name other types of breweries besides Spoetzl Brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8231499195098877,
            "question": "What industry does Spoetzl Brewery belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7618821263313293,
            "question": "Where would you likely find a brewery like Spoetzl Brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7410922646522522,
            "question": "Does Spoetzl Brewery produce food or beverages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3613969087600708,
            "question": "What is the main purpose of a brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34937170147895813,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of a brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.255300909280777,
            "question": "What is another word for 'brewery'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Spoetzl Brewery is a type of brewery.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4444_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics of a brewery?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4444_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main purpose of a brewery?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4444_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Spoetzl Brewery produce food or beverages?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4444_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4444_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Spoetzl Brewery is a type of brewery, as it is described as an independent craft brewery and its products (Shiner Beers) are referred to as beers."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly indicates that the Spoetzl Brewery is indeed a brewery. It mentions various aspects related to brewing and beer production, confirming its nature as a brewery."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}